<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
<channel>
<item id="1">
<title>MountainGarden Kennel</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/about/image1.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[When we decided we wanted to add a male to our family, our first thought was to get a puppy from Nala. Even before we got that far we were offered Blade, but since Nala is so stunningly beautiful and moreover, incredibly lovely, we felt her qualities need to be preserved for the future of the breed. Which is why we still want at least one litter from her. If you do something, better do it good, and make sure you can be proud of it, so we decided to do this under an own kennel name <a href="http://www.mountaingarden.nl">MountainGarden</a>. At the website you will find more details on our program and available puppies.]]></description>
<link>http://www.mountaingarden.nl</link>
</item>
<item id="2">
<title>Food</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/about/image2.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[We give our dogs dry food. We started with Royal Canin and will continue to use Medium Junior in the future for the first months. However Nala was not doing well on the food due to the corn addition. Someone gave us the good advice to try Doglovers Gold, a excellent quality food, about as rich in fat and proteines, but adding brown rice. Result; no more ear infections and irritations, and much more energy. Additional benefit, it's actually cheaper and get delivered at home. We combine it with some days of frozen raw meat meals, mostly Bandit or Duck.
In addition we give: Omega 3-6-9 capsules, yeast, carrots and apples (sometimes other fruit). Snacks are limited; dried pens, Pedigree Dentasticks, small trainers as reward.
To chew on we give Nylabones, the only thing that safely and lasting resists the chewing power of an Amstaff. They just chip of little pieces of nylon, that pass through the body undigested. For a toy we find the black Kong most suitable, but replace it the moment they starts to chew of little pieces (they can be quite harmfull).]]></description>
</item>
<item id="3">
<title>The luxury outdoors</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/about/image3.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[Our dogs live in house with us. Sometimes it is nice for them to stay outdoors as well. The garden would soon turn into something similar to a motorcross track if we'd let them loose. That also would be uncomfortable when having a barbecue So we created their own little paradise in a corner of the garden, that we, and them, are very proud of.
<img src="thumb/2008-05-28_nieuwe_huis-024t.jpg" width="200">
]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>