<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
<channel>
<item id="1">
<title>WHY AN AMSTAFF</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/home/image1.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[And all of a sudden comes that moment someone says; let's get a dog. Yeah, great idea, but what breed? Well .....
<li>Not to big, but not to small either. In any case it should be a 'real' dog, one a bit sturdy</li><li>Short hair, with little loss of hair and little maintenance (no trimming)</li><li>Healthy and strong. Not one of those breeds with lots of problems</li><li>With a lovely temper, especially around kids</li><li>Calm and reliable. Not a dog that will startle at nothing. Fearful dogs are the most unreliable</li><li>(OK, of course it would be a nice extra if burglars swould rather skip your house, so if it would scare those guys of, that would be a nice extra)</li>
All breeds were investigated and checked upon, but one breed clearly stood out. The American Staffordshire Terrier, or Amstaff for short. Beautiful dog, good size, easy to maintain coat, and so wonderfully calm and self confident.
But of course for a breed like that (well any breed really) you need to find a good, reliable breeder. Until recently an Amstaff without a valid pedigree was considered a Pitbull-type dog and could have been confiscated and brought to death. But even now that tjis law is abolished, it is still important to find a reliable serious breeder.
We are extremely happy with our choice, for Nala and Blade are truely everything we were looking for in a dog!
]]></description>
</item>
<item id="2">
<title>THE AMERICAN STAFFORDSHIRE TERRIER</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:39:42 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/home/image2.jpg</image>
<description> <![CDATA[To start with a common prejudice (and believe me, we did get these comments); what makes a nice little family take some 'Pitbull' into their home?<br>
Well, a step at a time, so other may benefit from our experience:
<li>In the Netherlands until recently Pitbulls and Pitbull-type dogs were prohibited by law. This was regulated by the Law Agressive Animals (RAD) in which a number of specific breeds were admitted, provided they had a valid and recognized pedigree. This included the Amstaff. It was therefore very, very important never to buy an Amstaff without a pedigree (for the sense of the law that would not be an Amstaff). Luckely the law was abolished June 2008, and replaced by legislation punishing the deed, not the breed. A good thing, but caution in once choice is still needed, and in the explosion of non-pedigree litters that can be expected in the aftermath, looking for a dog with pedigree may be wise. So inform yourself, and realize that cheap deals are not an option here. Of course it needs to be added that Pitbulls have a glorious history in the USA. As a result of the RAD, the Amstaff was a very popular breed at shows, since a very good show result for each parent was needed to obtain a pedigree for puppies.</li><li>Amstaffs are not scared easily, and can endure pain very well. It is ironic that these characteristics are why they are feared, while it is precisely what makes them such reliable dogs. They react very calmly and balanced to whatever happens in their environment, and can handle any situation both physically and mentally</li><li>They are really easy dogs in the house. Inside they generally are very calm</li><li>Amstaffs are great with kids. They really love all kids and if necessary will give their lives to protect them (and no, that does not imply agressive
behaviour)</li><li>If a Pitbull was good enough for Presidents Theodore Roosevelt and Woodrow Wilson (and not for G.W. Bush), and also for General George Patton, Fred Astaire, Humphrey Bogart, Thomas Edison, Madonna, Brad Pitt, Alicia Silverstone, Jamie Foxx, Jessica Biel, Jessica Alba, Michael J. Fox, Jan Michael Vincent, Jack Dempsey, Bernadette Peters, Linda Blair, Mel Brooks, Ann Bancroft, Pink and TV dog behavioural specialist <A HREF="http://www.cesarmillaninc.com/" target=_blank>Cesar Milan</A>, than surely an Amstaff will do fine for us!</li><li>It is the person behind the dog, not the dog, that constitutes the real danger</li>
On the site of the breed association <a href=http://www.astch.nl target=_blank>ASTCH</A> there is a lot of additional information on the American Staffordshire Terrier. We fully recommend the <a href=http://www.astch.nl/ASTCH_bestanden/rasinfogids.html target=_blank>guide</A> that is available with information, and an overview of known, reliable breeders. A good way to get to know the breed a little better is visit a dog show, or even better, one of the events of the ASTCH:
<li>In spring there is a Young Dog show, a somewhat more informal way to get started with shows and show a dog up to two years old</li><li>In summer there is a club event, just a nice gathering of people and dogs, with some demonstrations etc.</li><li>In November they organize the Dutch specialty</li>
These are good ocassions to see a lot of these dogs together, talk to owners about their experiences and get an impression of the various breeders. The <a href=http://www.astch.nl target=_blank>ASTCH</A> site provides more information on these events.]]></description>
</item>
<item id="3">
<title>SETTING AN EXAMPLE</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 03:39:42 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/home/image3.jpg</image>
<description> <![CDATA[We much desired our dogs, with all their enthusiasm, to become ambassadors to their breed, so wrongly judged. For us that means:
<li>We are convinced our dog should not be a burden or annoyance to others</li><li>Dog shit has no business in a neighbourhood</li><li>A dog should be on a leash, unless unleashed dogs are allowed <b><u>and</u></b> the owner has full control over the dog</li><li>Every dog, but even more their owners, should complete a proper obedience training. We did so with <a href="http://www.mgh-lelystad.nl/temp/" target=_blank>Martin Gaus</A> in Lelystad, with good results</li><li>Every dog should do a behavioural (MAG) test before it can be used to breed. This regardless of breed (or no breed) and size (beware of the small dogs). Nala has passed this MAG test with excellent results, Blade will; be tested when he reaches the proper age</li><li>Agressive behaviour will not be tolerated</li>
But, of course, this is all very easy for us. Nala is absolutely not dominant and will accept dominant (but not agressive) behaviour 
from other dogs, big or small. Towards people she is very friendly, and she just loves children. Blade is not very different and has a very free and open character.
]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>