<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
<channel>
<item id="1">
<title>CHICA</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 Sept 2008 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/memoriam/image1.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[No, no Amstaff this time, just a very remarkable cat.
<li>Chicca was an American shorthair cat, blue creme tortoise. A real american, the first time we saw Chica (pronounce Kika) at our holiday house in Italy she still worde an american address tag. There were several amercians living nearby that worked at the Aviano airbase. We expect that somehow Chica was left behind when they returned to the States.</li><li>When we returned back to the Netherlands two years later Chica came with us. She was so sweet with the kids and they really wanted to keep her.</li><li>Before we made the final decision we took her to the vet for a check. He found her in perfect condition, even after two years in the wild. She always stayed that way, strong and in excellent shape. She was totally OK with the visit to the vet, as if she understood the underlying intention.</li><li>At home she adapted easily. She stayed inside, but came with us on our holidays to Italy, where she roamed and hunted in her well known forest. She would even catch Ghiri, the local squirle (but contrary to mice, I do not believe she killed them)</li><li>They say cat attach to places, not people. That was not true for Chica. When we left for holiday (either way) she'd be waiting, ready to part. In Italy she'd pass by every evening to say goodnight, when we went somewhere she'd be waiting at the entrance at our return, and although she could disapear into the forest for hours, she'd be sitting patiently next to the car the day of departure.</li><li>When the kids cried she'd go over to comfort them, with licks, little soft bites and soft paw caresses. When the Jack Russell of Stefania's parent had the guts to bite Brian she had to run to stay out of Chica's claws!</li><li>When I was working behind the pc she'd come lie in from of me, preferably on the leyboard, demanding attention and hugs. If I dared continue to work, she'd push my hand with the mouse with her head, and if I insisted, softly bite in it. Then she'd stretch out to softly caress my cheek with her paw.</li>
Chica was fabulous and it was sad when after nine years she turned out to have kidney disease. We never knew exactly how old she was, but she must have been about 14 years old when she passed away. She's now resting peacefully in her beloved forest in Italy. No other cat will ever take her place.
]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>