<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
<channel>
<item id="1">
<title>Parastone's Creamy Cappuccino</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/nala/image01.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[When we had made our choice for the Amstaff as a breed we started to properly look around for a good breeder. At Parastones we found a match. The dogs grew up in the house, together with the breeder's family with two children, and two adult males lay calmly together under the table, sharing one bone. 'Founding male' Bimbo (Flamewood's Rainbow dragon) was a massive dog, but incredibly enthusiastic and friendly and immediately stole our hearts. His character has passed on to Nala, which gives us great pleasure. Nala is a daughter of another very successful male, Parastone's Don't Panic (Dexter), who showed on the cover of the breed association magazin in 2005, as best Amstaff bred in the Netherlands. Dexter is an easy, pleasant dog (son of Bimbo) and that shows in Nala. 
Nala is blue fawn with white, a color pattern which is referred to in her pedigree name; Parastone's Creamy Cappuccino. Her given name is Nala, after the lioness from Disney's Lion King. As for build and color we thought that was appropriate as well. The most beautiful and eye catching quality of Nala is her head. It's big and broad, with the recognizable strong and large jaws. But combined with the intensly sweet expression and almost human eyes, it should be clear to everyone immediately that she would never harm anyone (especially for burglars: no guarantees beyond the garden doors!).
]]></description>
<link>http://www.mountaingarden.nl</link>
</item>
<item id="2">
<title>Show results</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/nala/image02.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[Nala has done excellent at shows:
<li>Dutch Champion</li><li>Dutch Specialty Winner 2007 (CW'07)</li><li>Brabo Winner '08</li><li>Reserve best Amstaff 2007</li><li>5<sup>th</sup> best Dutch terrier 2007</li><li>7 x CAC</li><li>4 x CACIB</li><li>1 x RCACIB</li><li>3 x BOB</li><li>3 x BOS</li><li>1 x 2<sup>nd</sup> BIG</li><li>1 x 5<sup>th</sup> BIG</li><li>1 x BIS</li><li>25 x Excellent in 25 FCI shows</li>
Up to date show news can be found on our kennel site, click below for details.
]]></description>
<link>http://www.mountaingarden.nl</link>
</item>
<item id="3">
<title>Our baby</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 11:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
<image>image/nala/image03.jpg</image>
<description><![CDATA[Above all Nala is a member of our family. She lives inside with us and goes on holiday with us. She is our best friend, bringing comfort when things are down, and sharing the joy when things go well. She is inseparable from our son Brian, and you can find them togther, embraced, on her dog pillow while Brian reads a book.
In house Nala is quite calm, even a bit lazy. She loves warmth, and in wintertime she enjoys being entirely wrapped up in her blanket by us.
Nala loves everyone, and needs to greet everybody with enthusiasm. But she sure knows when someone approaches the house other than through the front door, and she'll be 100% watchful.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>