<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content>
	<e des="About Designer's Portfolio" columns="2" croptitle="true">
		<column1>
			<![CDATA[<b>Designer’s portfolio features a unique website template with  great motion, a clean design and deeplinking support. This template comes with over 65 predefined settings in config.xml, total freedom in the setup of your pages and a user manual counting 40 pages. Here are some of the features of this template:</b><br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Header:</font></b><br>You are completely free in which buttons to add to the website and which templates to attach to those buttons. For example, this allows you to create multiple projects sections or add several text pages.<br>Also you can enable of disable visibility of the logo, change its text or use your own logo instead.<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Footer:</font></b><br>Customize the footer text, allow fullscreen mode of the website and turn on and off the music.<img src="img/textimage1.png" align="left" hspace="0" vspace="3"/><br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Sound:</font></b><br>Turn on and off the interface sound fx, load a complete mp3 playlist and listen to the music fading in and out between songs and when set to pause.<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Deeplinking:</font></b><br>Deeplinking allows the visitor to use the back and forward button of the browser. Even more important: it’s possible to directly access a certain page or project in the website itself. Try for instance <a href="asfunction:_global.base.setAddress,portfolio/project4">clicking on this link</a>!<br><br>6 available templates to use for this website:<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">News:</font></b><br>Set your own headlines and use the cool way to scroll them through your screen.  With deeplinking it is possible to directly access projects from your headlines using HTML links.]]>
		</column1>
		<column2>
			<![CDATA[<b><font color="#EB325C">Projects:</font></b><br>Scroll through the thumbnails in a unique way. When opening a project the project is able to show images, videos and swf files. See popup descriptions when rolling over the media items. Furthermore, images can be viewed fullscreen and feature a magnifying glass when able to zoom in.<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Large texts: </font></b><br>Create larger pieces of text (like this one) and define whether it should be divided in 1 or 2 columns. The scrollbar will adjust its height to the height of the website. The text supports <i>HTML tags</i>, <a href="http://www.flashden.net/user/Webmarbles" target="_blank">CSS decorated hyperlinks</a>, special àáâãäå æçèéêë<img src="img/textimage2.png" align="left" hspace="0" vspace="3"/>ìíîïñò óôöõ÷ øùúûüý character support and image support! A hyperlink to other supported tags is provided in the user manual!<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Contact: </font></b><br>Set your contact details simply by adjusting an xml file. Easily customize the contact form to your needs! PHP file for sending contact info included.<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Insert your own SWF: </font></b><br>Be able to insert your own Flash movie to the website.<br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Use external links: </font></b><br>Easily create external links in the main navigation.<br><br><br><b><font color="#EB325C">Download file contains: </font></b><br>- All source files and assets used for the demo as shown here<br>- FLA files with all code commented<br>- More than 30 pages of user manual<br><br>Fonts used are Verdana and Century Gothic which are not included in the download package. Pictures by Mark Lenssen. Background music by <a href="http://www.audiojungle.net/user/ADG3studios">ADG3studios</a>. Thanks guys!]]>
		</column2>
	</e>

</content>